I have fallen in love with you.
لقد وقعت في حبك.
Brother Qi,
الأخ تشي ،
I'm just a friend
أنا مجرد صديق
to you.
لك.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
You care more about Wen Qi
أنت تهتم أكثر بشأن Wen Qi
than I do,
مما أفعل ،
Did I?
هل فعلت؟
I don't know if you've noticed,
لا أعرف ما إذا كنت قد لاحظت ،
but you always call me Brother Qi.
لكنك دائمًا تناديني يا أخي تشي.
Instead, I'll call him Tang Wenqi.
بدلاً من ذلك ، سأتصل به تانغ وينكي.
I knew it from the moment I found out about it.
لقد عرفت ذلك منذ اللحظة التي اكتشفت فيها ذلك.
I'm just a friend
أنا مجرد صديق
to you.
لك.
-I'm sorry. -Brother Qi.
-أنا آسف.  - الأخ تشي.
I finally found you two.
أخيرا وجدت لكم اثنين.
Aren't you studying?
الا تدرسين
We need to combine work and rest.
نحن بحاجة إلى الجمع بين العمل والراحة.
I suggest,
أقترح،
taking advantage of the rest time,
الاستفادة من وقت الراحة ،
How about hosting a welcome dinner for Chestnut?
ماذا عن استضافة عشاء ترحيبي للكستناء؟
Wen Qi just told me that he wants to treat me to roast duck
أخبرني وين تشي للتو أنه يريد أن يعالجني لتحميص البط
and drink a lot of wine?
وتشرب الكثير من النبيذ؟
When did you two become so close?
متى أصبحتا قريبين جدا؟
I'm telling you,
أنا أخبرك،
Wen Qi is the most passionate person I've ever met.
Wen Qi هو الشخص الأكثر شغفًا الذي قابلته على الإطلاق.
Chestnut is cute, too.
الكستناء لطيف أيضًا.
I won't take part in it.
لن أشارك فيه.
Brother Qi,
الأخ تشي ،
are you kidding me?
هل تمزح معي؟
We, the Four Masters of Gu Yuan,
نحن ، سادة جو يوان الأربعة ،
are indispensable.
لا غنى عنها.
I have something to do at home.
لدي شيء لأفعله في المنزل.
Brother Qi,
الأخ تشي ،
please, please.
من فضلك من فضلك.
Okay, okay.
حسنا حسنا.
Okay,
تمام،
I'll go.
سأذهب.
It's a deal then.
إنها صفقة إذن.
Okay.
تمام.
Have you seen my work?
هل رأيت عملي؟
How am I supposed to know about your own stuff?
كيف لي أن أعرف عن الأشياء الخاصة بك؟
No,
لا،
I didn't throw it away either.
أنا لم أرميها بعيدًا أيضًا.
Think about it,
فكر في الأمر،
did Brother Qi help you revise your work today?
هل ساعدك Brother Qi في مراجعة عملك اليوم؟
Is it in the closet?
هل هو في الخزانة؟
I think so.
أعتقد ذلك.
What did you
ماذا فعلت
find?
يجد؟
Brother Qi is moving out.
الأخ تشي ينتقل.
Is there anything
هل يوجد أي شئ
bothering Brother Qi lately?
يزعج الأخ تشي مؤخرا؟
He didn't even want to go to the reception banquet that day.
لم يكن يريد حتى الذهاب إلى مأدبة الاستقبال في ذلك اليوم.
That's not right.
هذا غير صحيح.
He is excellent in character and learning.
إنه ممتاز في الشخصية والتعلم.
What troubles can there be?
ما هي المشاكل التي يمكن أن تكون هناك؟
Did we mess with him?
هل عبثنا معه؟
I … I didn't.
أنا ... لم أفعل.
I haven't seen much of him in the past two days.
لم أر الكثير منه في اليومين الماضيين.
Then why?
إذن لماذا؟
I've been studying so hard recently,
لقد كنت أدرس بجد مؤخرًا ،
and he praised me.
وامتدحني.
Is it because of me?
هل هو بسببي؟
No matter what the reason is,
بغض النظر عن السبب ،
we don't want Brother Qi to leave.
لا نريد أن يغادر Brother Qi.
Right?
يمين؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
All right. You must listen to me.
حسنًا.  يجب أن تستمع إلي.
Don't tell anyone
لا تخبر أحدا
about what happened today.
حول ما حدث اليوم.
But on the day of the welcome banquet,
ولكن في يوم مأدبة الترحيب ،
you must give Brother Qi and I half an hour.
يجب أن تمنح الأخ تشي وأنا نصف ساعة.
You're not trying to
أنت لا تحاول
seduce him.
تغويه.
Tang Wenqi,
تانغ وينكي ،
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
Mr. Shan is here.
السيد شان هنا.
Li,
لي ،
come on.
تعال.
Let's have a seat.
دعونا نجلس.
What about Wu Wancheng?
ماذا عن Wu Wancheng؟
It's okay. He has Brother Qi?
لا بأس.  لديه الأخ تشي؟
Brother Qi,
الأخ تشي ،
have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
I saved a seat for you.
لقد قمت بحفظ مقعد لك.
No, thanks.
ًلا شكرا.
I'll sit here.
سأجلس هنا.
Look,
ينظر،
I told you there must be something wrong with them.
أخبرتك أنه لا بد من وجود شيء خاطئ معهم.
Ling Xiu
لينغ زيو
I've told you.
لقد قلت لك.
Call me Miss Feng.
اتصل بي آنسة فنغ.
Yes,
نعم،
Miss Feng,
ملكة جمال فنغ ،
Tell me,
أخبرني،
why do you come to me again?
لماذا تاتي الي مرة اخرى
I … I sprained my ankle, but why are you covering your
أنا ... لويت كاحلي ، لكن لماذا تقوم بتغطية كاحلي
knee?
ركبة؟
I hurt my knee, too.
لقد أصبت ركبتي أيضًا.
Look.
ينظر.
I … I can't even stand still now.
أنا ... لا أستطيع حتى أن أقف مكتوفي الأيدي الآن.
All right,
حسنًا،
stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
Actually, I want to ask you,
في الواقع أريد أن أسألك ،
how are you thinking about getting married?
كيف تفكر في الزواج
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
You
أنت
promised me.
وعدني.
Today,
اليوم،
I'll fill in the song
سأملأ الأغنية
I didn't finish last time.
لم أنهي آخر مرة.
Qi Shan,
تشي شان ،
get up and talk about the artistic conception of that song.
انهض وتحدث عن المفهوم الفني لتلك الأغنية.
Qishan,
قيشان ،
I'm calling you.
أنا أتصل بك هاتفيا او انا أناديك.
Mr. Shan,
السيد.  شان ،
student,
طالب،
I didn't hear you clearly.
لم أسمعك بوضوح.
You didn't hear me clearly?
ألم تسمعني بوضوح؟
Or Sichun?
أو Sichun؟
Chen Lan,
تشين لان ،
Smell it
شمها
Who farted?
من الذي اخرج ريحا؟
It stinks.
ينتن.
Boss,
رئيس،
you really have no quality.
ليس لديك جودة حقًا.
Who are you talking about?
عن من تتكلم؟
Who let me say who?
من دعني أقول من؟
All right, all right.
حسنا حسنا.
Stop messing around.
توقف عن العبث.
The final exam is approaching,
الامتحان النهائي يقترب ،
Qishan Qi
كيشان تشي
I hope you can
أتمنى أن تتمكن من ذلك
remember your status as a student,
تذكر حالتك كطالب ،
It's your duty to study.
من واجبك أن تدرس.
Okay,
تمام،
sit down.
اجلس.
Mr. Xie.
السيد شيه.
If it weren't for our Li,
إذا لم يكن لي ،
I wouldn't have taken out
لم أكن لأخرج
the wine I've collected for so many years,
النبيذ الذي جمعته لسنوات عديدة ،
Come and try my peerless wine.
تعال وجرب نبيذي منقطع النظير.
Thank you, bro.
شكرا اخي.
Let's drink till we drop.
دعونا نشرب حتى نسقط.
Come on,
تعال،
Why did I forget about the roast duck?
لماذا نسيت البطة المشوية؟
Chestnut,
كستناء،
Well,
حسنًا،
Can you go get a roast duck with me at the door?
هل يمكنك الذهاب لإحضار بطة مشوية معي عند الباب؟
Okay.
تمام.
Then come with me, Lingxiu.
ثم تعال معي ، Lingxiu.
I'm not going.
أنا لن أذهب.
I want to be with Sister Wu,
أريد أن أكون مع الأخت وو ،
Lingxiu,
Lingxiu ،
Get me two more cucumbers
أحضر لي خيارين إضافيين
to get rid of the boredom.
للتخلص من الملل.
Go,
يذهب،
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
You asked them to leave, didn't you?
طلبت منهم المغادرة ، أليس كذلك؟
It's a little obvious.
من الواضح قليلا.
If Wen Qi hadn't begged me,
إذا لم يتوسل وين تشي لي ،
I wouldn't have shown up.
لم أكن لأظهر.
I'm not blaming you.
أنا لا ألومك.
I think we should make it clear.
أعتقد أننا يجب أن نوضح ذلك.
You and I know each other very well.
أنت وأنا نعرف بعضنا البعض جيدًا.
I'll try not to disturb you.
سأحاول ألا أزعجك.
Brother Qi,
الأخ تشي ،
I never wanted you to leave.
لم أرد منك أن تغادر.
You didn't do anything wrong.
أنت لم تفعل شيئًا خاطئًا.
That's why you don't have to hide from me.
هذا هو السبب في أنك لست مضطرًا للاختباء عني.
Between us,
بيننا،
it's still the same as before,
لا يزال كما كان من قبل ،
Is that okay?
هل هذا مقبول؟
We can still be the same as before,
لا يزال بإمكاننا أن نكون كما كان من قبل ،
of course,
بالطبع،
You'll always be my brother Qi.
ستكون دائمًا أخي تشي.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I thought
اعتقدت
you were imagining things,
كنت تتخيل الأشياء ،
Have you forgotten what we told Tang Wenqi?
هل نسيت ما قلناه لـ Tang Wenqi؟
If you have anything to say, let's solve it together.
إذا كان لديك أي شيء لتقوله ، فلنحل المشكلة معًا.
I'm sorry
أنا آسف
for letting you down.
لإحباطك.
It doesn't exist.
لا وجود لها.
So don't even think about leaving the supervisor.
لذلك لا تفكر حتى في ترك المشرف.
Stay here.
ابق هنا.
Oh no.
أوه لا.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I just handed in the application for retirement,
لقد سلمت للتو طلب التقاعد ،
and I'm afraid you've already seen it,
وأخشى أنك رأيته بالفعل ،
Why don't you go and get it back?
لماذا لا تذهب وتستعيدها؟
I'll get it back.
سأستعيدها.
Don't wait for me.
لا تنتظرني.
Hurry up.
أسرع - بسرعة.
It will be great if this matter is solved.
سيكون رائعًا إذا تم حل هذه المسألة.
Where's Qi?
أين Qi؟
Why is it missing?
لماذا هو مفقود؟
He went to get his retirement application.
ذهب للحصول على طلب التقاعد الخاص به.
He did hand it in.
لقد سلمها.
If I had known, I would have torn it up.
لو كنت أعرف ، لكنت مزقتها.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
All right. It's all in the past.
حسنًا.  كل شيء في الماضي.
Guys,
شباب،
Kai Xuan,
كاي شوان
Here we are.
نحن هنا.
Cheers!
هتافات!